Guide to the Administrative Papers of the President George Bugliarello RG.006
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series III: Polytechnic, 7
  - Subseries A: Honorary Degrees, 1957-1986; 1218
    - Honorary Degrees - Miscellaneous, 1980-1981; 1228 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Honorary Degrees - Miscellaneous, 1982-1985; 1226 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Honorary Degrees - Miscellaneous, 1988, Undated; 1229 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Subseries B: SUNY Merger, 1965-1974; 1277
    - SUNY Merger – A-5, 1969 March - 1972 January; 1278 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - SUNY Merger – B (Budget), 1968-1972; 1279 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - SUNY Merger – C-1, 1968-1970; 1280 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - SUNY Merger – C-2, 1971 Fall; 1281 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - SUNY Merger – C-2 – 1, 1967-1970; 1282 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - SUNY Merger – C-2 – 2, 1966-1970; 1283 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - SUNY Merger – C-3 - 1, 1968-1970; 1284 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - SUNY Merger – C-3 - 2, 1968-1970; 1285 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - SUNY Merger – D 1 – 1, 1970-1972; 1286 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - SUNY Merger – D 1 – 2, 1971-1973; 1287 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - SUNY Merger – D 2 – 1, 1968-1974; 1288 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - SUNY Merger – D 2 – 2, 1969-1972; 1289 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - SUNY Merger – E, 1968-1970; 1290 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - SUNY Merger Contract, 1972-1973; 1291 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - SUNY Merger Plans – Faculty 1, 1970-1971; 1292 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - SUNY Merger Plans – Faculty 2, 1970; 1293 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - SUNY Merger Plans – Faculty 3, 1970; 1294 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - SUNY Merger – Willenbroch Letter Index & Correspondence - 1, 1968-1969; 1295 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - SUNY Merger – Willenbroch Letter Index & Correspondence - 2, 1965, 1970; 1296 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - SUNY Merger – Campus Master Program Guide for Facilities, Undated; 1297 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - SUNY Merger - Senator Bloom, 1968 May–1971 April; 1298 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - SUNY Merger – Miscellaneous, 1966-1972 January; 1299 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Subseries C: NYU-SES Merger, 7146
    - Notes and correspondence, 1974; 7148 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Meeting notes, 1975; 7147 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Reports, 1973-1976; 7149 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Clippings, 1974; 7150 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Subseries D: Education Committee of the Board of Trustees, 1970-1983; 1300
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1970-1971 February; 1301 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1971 December-1974 August; 1302 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1974 October-December; 1303 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1975; 1304 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1975-1976; 1305 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1976-1977; 1306 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1977-1978; 1307 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1978-1979; 1308 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1979-1980; 1309 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1980-1981; 1310 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1982 July-1983 February; 1311 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1983 January-March; 1312 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1983 March-December; 1313 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1982-1983; 1370 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Subseries E: Polytechnic Corporation Committees, 1981-1993; 1369
    - Education Committee of the Corporation, 1984 May-1985 November; 1371 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Education Committee of the Corporation – Minutes, Agenda, 1985-1986; 1372 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Education Committee of the Corporation – Long-term Neighborhood Plan, 1985-1986; 1373 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Education Committee of the Corporation – Honorary Degrees, 1985-1986; 1374 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Education Committee of the Corporation, 1986 May-November; 1375 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Education Committee of the Corporation, 1986 December-1987 January; 1376 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Education Committee of the Corporation, 1987 February-March; 1377 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Education Committee of the Corporation, 1987 May-1988 April; 1378 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Education Committee of the Corporation, Undated; 1379 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Polytechnic University - Finance Committee, 1986 May-1987 April; 1380 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Polytechnic University – Departmental Overviews, 1986 April-1987 April; 1381 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Polytechnic University – Departments, 1986; 1382 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Engineering Self-Study, 1986; 1383 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Polytechnic University – Bylaws, 1981; 1384 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Polytechnic University – Corporation – 3 Year Budget Projection, 1983 December-1984 November; 1385 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Polytechnic University – Ad Hoc Evaluations For Institute Professorship Nominees, 1984; 1386 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Polytechnic University – Corporation Committees, 1983-1985; 1387 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Polytechnic University – Resolution of the Corporation, 1986 March; 1388 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Polytechnic University – Published Speeches, 1979-1993; 1389 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Subseries F: Board Meeting Minutes, 1984-1987; 1390
    - Executive Committee Meeting - September 1, 1986, 1986 March-October; 1391 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Polytechnic University – Campaign Report, 1986 October 21; 1392 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Polytechnic University – Executive Committee, 1986 May-June; 1393 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Polytechnic University – Meeting of the Corporation, 1984 August-1986 June; 1394 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Polytechnic University – Executive Committee Meeting, 1986 February-July; 1395 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Polytechnic University – Administrative – Miscellaneous, 1986 March-July; 1396 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Polytechnic University – Corporation Meetings – Hotel Reservation, 1985 August-1986 April; 1397 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Polytechnic University – Executive Committee Meeting, 1985 December 5; 1398 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Polytechnic University – Executive Committee Meeting, 1985 October 15; 1399 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Polytechnic University – Executive Committee Meeting, 1985 September 12; 1400 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Polytechnic University - Corporation Meeting, 1986 January 16; 1401 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Polytechnic University – Corporation Meeting, 1985 January 17; 1402 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Polytechnic University – Board Retreat, 1986 April-November; 1403 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Polytechnic University – Corporation Retreat Response Forms, October-November 1986, 1986 July-November; 1404 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Polytechnic University – Corporation Meetings – Miscellaneous, 1984 November-1986 March; 1405 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Polytechnic University – Corporation Meetings – Miscellaneous, 1986 April-May, Undated; 1406 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Polytechnic University – President's Report Master List, 1986 June-1987 June; 1407 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Polytechnic University - Executive Committee Meeting, February 14, 1985, 1984 November-1985 February; 1408 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Subseries G: Board Members, 1968-1990; 1409
    - Adler, Benjamin (Emeritus), 1975 June-1990 July; 1419 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Albert, Sidney G., 1985 June-1989 March; 1420 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Angermueller, Hans H., 1985 September-1988 December; 1421 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Baclini, David, 1979 September-1986 April; 1415 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Bloom, Jeremiah B., 1980 January-1983 October; 1422 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Brown, Joseph D., 1975 June, 1980 June; 1414 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Bruynes, Cees, 1983 July-1989 May; 1423 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Buchanan, Harry W., 1979 June-1987 August; 1424 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Catacosinos, William, 1980 October-1984 October; 1425 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Conigliaro, Salvatore A., Undated; 1413 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Dalton, Philip B., 1979 July-December; 1412 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Dibner, Bern, Honorary Trustee, 1979 November-1988 August; 1418 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Fromm, Dr. Winfield E., 1978 August-1983 July; 1411 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Gavin, Joseph G., 1976 January-1983 November; 1426 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Habach, George F., Emeritus Trustee, 1973 September-1989 May; 1427 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Hickey, Frank, 1980 May-1981 March; 1417 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Hoffman, Harmon F., 1979 September–1987 August; 1428 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Laubach, Gerald D., 1980 October–1987 May; 1429 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Leistner, William E., 1968 May-1990 March; 1430 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Lewis, Dr. Robert E. (Emeritus), 1975 June-1983 July; 1431 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Llewelyn-Davies, Richard, 1978 June-1981 June; 1432 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Mark, Herman F., 1975 June-1989 May; 1433 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Mitchel, David C., 1975 June, 1984 July; 1434 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Newman, Joseph, 1985 June-1988 July; 1435 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Nisenson, Stanley M., 1983 August-1987 September; 1436 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Pascal, Donald D., 1975 June-1988 June; 1437 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Pighi, Louis H., 1983 July-1990 January; 1438 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Rogee, Dr. Herbert H., 1975 June-1977 September; 1410 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Simmonds, Geoffrey R., 1985 September-1986 December; 1416 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Smith, Harrison V., 1980 February-1988 July; 1439 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Westerman, David, 1980 March-1989 May; 1440 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Subseries H: Miscellaneous, 1441
    - Administrative Officer's Directory, 1990; 1442 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Agendas, 1993 June-August, 1994 January; 1443 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Agendas, 1993 December; 1444 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Alumni Development & Fundraising, 1991-1993; 1445 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Annual Meeting of the Corporation, 1993 May 26; 1446 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Appointment Book, 1990; 1447 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - ASME Region II, Graduate Student Technical Conference, 1993 April 16; 1448 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Board of Overseers – Peer Comparison, University of Pennsylvania, 1981 January-March; 1449 (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - Board of Trustees Recruitment, 1990 December; 1450 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - Budget, 1991 March-1992 September; 1451 (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - Budget, 1980-1983; 2015 (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - Car Phone, NYNEX, 1991 March; 1452 (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - Center for Technology and Financial Services, 1992; 1453 (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - C.T.F. – Contacts, Undated; 1454 (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - C.T.F. - Proposal, 1992; 1455 (Box 30, Folder 54)
    - C.T.F. – St. Johns, 1993 March-December, Undated; 1456 (Box 30, Folder 55)
    - Center for Telecommunications Technology, Draft, Undated; 1457 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Chemistry Department, 1968 May-1975 March; 1458 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1975 November, 1979 April; 1459 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Clippings - Hi-Tech Universities, 1982 April-1983 April; 1460 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Clippings – Hi-Tech Universities, 1984 February-1985 June; 1461 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Clipping Book, 1980-1987; 1462 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Complaint - RESTRICT, 1978; 1463 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Contacts, 1984-1986; 1464 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Corporation, 1993 March-December; 1465 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Corporation, 1994 January, March; 1466 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Corporation – Budget Reports, 1987 October-1992 October; 1467 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Corporation – Fiscal Year 1994, 1468 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Corporation – Miscellaneous, 1987 June-1992 March; 1469 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Corporation Annual Meeting Minutes, 1993 July 26; 1470 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Corporation Meeting, 1993 January 21; 1471 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Corporation Meetings, 1993 March-May; 1472 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Corporation Meetings, 1993 March-1994 April; 1473 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1976 December–1977 May; 1474 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1977 March-December; 1475 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1978 February-September; 1476 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1978 September; 1477 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1992 May-October; 1478 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1990 February-1993 June; 1479 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1991 June-1993 December; 1480 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1992 February–1993 December; 1481 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1992 December-1993 July; 1482 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1992 May-1993 June; 1483 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1993 May-September; 1484 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1993 December-1994 April; 1485 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1993 January-1994 March; 1486 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1993 October-1994 March; 1487 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, Undated; 1488 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence - Regis University, 1993 November 12; 1489 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Course Development – Engineering, 1992 November; 1490 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - C.W. Hoover, 1992 November; 1491 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Department of Civil Engineering Corporation Visiting Committee, 1989 May-1992 November; 1497 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Departmental Reports, 1987 December-1990 August; 1498 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Development - Jeffrey Stewart Visit, 1993 March; 1492 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Development – Memorandum, 1992; 1496 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Development - Paul Steck Visit, 1993 February-March; 1493 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Development Committee, 1992 September-1994 January; 1494 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Directions To/From Campus, Undated; 1495 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Donations, 1990 December; 1499 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Eli Pearce - N.Y. Institute of Chemists Awards, 1991-1992; 1500 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Engineering Colleges, Legislatures and Community, 1977; 1501 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Engineering Department 5-year Plan, 1981-1986; 1502 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Engineering, Science & Management Education, 1986 April; 1503 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Enrollment Memo, 1994 February; 1504 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1992 November 24; 1505 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Expenses, 1986-1987; 1506 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Faculty, 1989 September-1992 November; 1507 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Financial Services Technology Consortium (FINTECH), 1993 June; 1508 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Fiscal Year Budgets, 1991-1994; 1509 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Fundraising, 1984-1989 April; 1510 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Fundraising, 1987 December-1988 November, Undated; 1511 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Fundraising - Poly 100 Newsletter, 1994 Winter; 1512 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Grant Proposals – National Science Foundation, 1992; 1513 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Holiday Cards, 1992, Undated; 1514 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Holiday Gift from the Bugliarellos, 1991; 1515 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Honorary Degree Recipients, 1984-1985; 1516 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Inaugural Address – Technology, the University and the Community, 1975 March 13; 1517 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - The Intelligent Layman's Guide to Technology, 1990; 1518 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - International Student Orientation, 1990-1991; 1519 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Invoices, 1992 April-October; 1520 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Kyoto University – Poly Academic Exchange, 1990 April-1992 June; 1521 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Leadership Candidates, 1988 August; 1522 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Letter to the Faculty, Drafts, 1989 July-August; 1523 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - L.I.C. Farmingdale, 1993 May 13; 1524 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - L.I.C. Westinghouse Site Acquisition, 1993 January; 1525 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Marconi International Fellowship, 1992 October; 1526 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Meeting, 1992 November 16; 1527 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Meeting of the Corporation, 1993 January 21; 1528 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Members of the Corporation, Lists, 1977-1986; 1529 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Memo to the Corporation, Draft, 1990 March; 1530 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Memos – Miscellaneous, Undated; 1531 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Microwave Research Institute, 1973; 1532 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Middle States Association – Accreditation Visit Spring 1992, 1533 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Middle States Association, 1982 June, 1987 June; 1534 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Middle States Association, 1990 April-November; 1535 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous, 1985; 1989 July-1992 October; 1536 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992 June, 1993 September; 1537 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993 January-May; 1538 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - New Initiatives Meeting, 1994 November; 1539 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - New Poly Curriculum – George Bugliarello Notes & Research, 1980 May-1985 January; 1540 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - New Poly Curriculum – George Bugliarello Notes & Research, 1985 February-May, Undated; 1541 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Office of the President – Purchasing, 1992 August-December; 1542 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Office of University Development – Correspondence, 1958 February-1975 December; 1543 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Office of the University Relations – Strategic Plan, 1992 April 27; 1544 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Overheads for Alumni Association Annual Meeting, 1990 June 11; 1545 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1977 March; 1546 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Phone Directories – Trustees & All University, 1988-1992; 1547 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - President's Associates List, 1986-1987; 1548 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - President's Financial Statements, 1992-1993; 1549 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - President's Report to the Corporation, 1975-1988, 1993; 1550 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Presidential Search, 1991 March-December; 1551 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Professional Appointment Book, 1986; 1553 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Professional Appointment Book, 1987; 1554 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Professional Appointment Book, 1988; 1555 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Professional Appointment Book, 1989; 1556 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Professional Appointment Calendar (Weekly), 1990; 1557 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Promise Fund / Poly 100, 1993 March-May; 1558 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Promise Fund Distinguished Service Award, 1994; 1559 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Promotional Material, 1978, 1988; 1560 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Promotional Material, 1988, 1992; 1561 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Promotional Material, 1992-1993; 1562 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Promotional Material, 1993-1994; 1563 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Proposal to Teagle Foundation, 1993-1994; 1564 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Publication – Invention and Education, 1977; 1567 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Report to Trustees, Drafts, 1988 May-1989 December; 1568 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Research at Poly, an Overview, 1990; 1569 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Robert Meyers, Trustee – Correspondence, 1993 March; 1570 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Rudolph Marcus Nobel Prize, 1992 October; 1571 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - School of Engineering & Applied Sciences (SEAS) – Duke University model, 1980-1981; 1572 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Search Committee, Faculty Head, Computer Science, 1985 October; 1573 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Search Committee, Faculty Head, Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering, 1985 January-1986 March; 1574 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Search Committee, Physics Head, 1985 August; 1575 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Self Study, 1992 October-1993 March; 1576 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Space Electronics Institute, 1986 April; 1577 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Staff Bios - RESTRICT, Undated; 1578 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Stanley Prill – Dinner, 1993 July; 1579 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - State Education Department – Correspondence, 1993 September; 1580 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Strategic Assessment Proposal, KPMG, 1992 August; 1581 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Strategic Plan, 1992 October 1; 1582 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Strategic Planning Meeting, 1993 November; 1583 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Student Complaint - RESTRICT, 1993 January-February; 1584 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Student Contact Information - RESTRICT, 1991, 1993; 1585 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Student Council Meeting, 1989 July 12; 1586 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Student Handbook, 1988; 1587 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Suggestion Box, 1976-1977; 1588 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Dr. Sun Honorary Degree, 1993 February-March; 1589 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Symposium – Polymer Science in the Next Decade, 1985 May; 1590 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Symposium Programs – Electrical Engineering & Computer Science, 1985 September; 1591 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Visiting Committee of the School of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, 1993 November; 1593 (Box 33, Folder 44)
- Series IV: Organizations, 10
  This series is arranged topically into 8 subseries.
  This series contains correspondence, memoranda, clippings, articles, meeting minutes and miscellaneous documents documenting George Bugliarello's role as member, trustee and elected official of a wide array educational, scientific, governmental and social organizations and associations.
  - Subseries A: Analytic Services (ANSER), 1987-1993; 1903
    - ANSER - Correspondence, Memoranda, 1987 November-1989 January; 1904 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - ANSER - Correspondence, Memoranda, 1990 March-1991 September; 1905 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - ANSER - Correspondence, Memoranda, 1991 October-1992 April; 1906 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - ANSER - Correspondence, Memoranda, 1992 April-1993 February, Undated; 1907 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Subseries B: Board on Science & Technology for International Development (BOSTID), 20
    - BOSTID - Miscellaneous, 1975-1980 August; 1246 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - BOSTID - Miscellaneous, 1980 September-1981 May; 1253 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - BOSTID - Miscellaneous, 1981 September-December; 1252 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - BOSTID - Miscellaneous, 1982 January-April; 1248 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - BOSTID - Miscellaneous, 1982 May-November; 1242 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - BOSTID - Miscellaneous, 1982 December; 1247 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - BOSTID - Miscellaneous, 1983 January-November; 1243 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - BOSTID - Miscellaneous, Undated; 1244 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - BOSTID – Annual Program Plan, 1981 July 1-1982 June 30; 1254 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - BOSTID - Governing Board, 1980 October; 1251 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - BOSTID - Innovation Program, 1993 June; 1256 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - BOSTID - Meeting, 1982 Aril 23; 1241 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - BOSTID - Membership, 1980-1983; 1255 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - BOSTID - Retreat, 1983 June 24-26; 1250 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Subseries C: National Academy of Engineering (NAE), 18
    - National Academy of Engineering - Miscellaneous, 1989 December-1993 December; 1257 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - National Academy of Engineering - Miscellaneous, 1994 January-March; 1258 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - National Academy of Engineering - Correspondence, 1992 July; 1259 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - National Academy of Engineering – Infrastructure, 1989 May-1991 June, Undated; 1260 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - National Academy of Engineering - Nominations, 1975 March-1978, 1988; Undated; 1261 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - National Academy of Engineering - Steering Committee, 1978 November; 1262 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Subseries D: New York City Partnership, 1979-1995; 1911
    - NYC Partnership - Miscellaneous, 1979-1980; 1912 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - NYC Partnership – Miscellaneous, 1981; 1913 (Box 35, Folder 5)